https://www.asante.com/asante-privacy-policy/

HomeThe CompanyAbout AsanteReviews and EventsPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseAsante ProductsSmart Garage Door OpenerChristmas Light Show CreatorRobot Vacuum CleanerDramatic GarageAsante ServicesFAQ for Asante Smart Home ProductsQuick GuidesContact UsBlogShop NowHomeThe CompanyAbout AsanteReviews and EventsPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseAsante ProductsSmart Garage Door OpenerChristmas Light Show CreatorRobot Vacuum CleanerDramatic GarageAsante ServicesFAQ for Asante Smart Home ProductsQuick GuidesContact UsBlogShop NowCALL US: (408) 435 8388 HomeThe CompanyAbout AsanteReviews and EventsPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseAsante ProductsSmart Garage Door OpenerChristmas Light Show CreatorRobot Vacuum CleanerDramatic GarageAsante ServicesFAQ for Asante Smart Home ProductsQuick GuidesContact UsBlogShop NowHomeThe CompanyAbout AsanteReviews and EventsPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseAsante ProductsSmart Garage Door OpenerChristmas Light Show CreatorRobot Vacuum CleanerDramatic GarageAsante ServicesFAQ for Asante Smart Home ProductsQuick GuidesContact UsBlogShop NowLegalAsante Privacy PolicyAsante PoliciesSep 24, 2019Privacy PolicyMaintaining customer privacy is important to Asante. The following information is available to help you understand how Asante protects customer information. Privacy PolicyPlease read this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to learn more about the manner in which we collect and use information that is generated when you(“User”) visit and interact with Asante’s website (the “Site”), Asante products, systems, including any and all devices, applications and other digital and interactive services. If you visit the Site and/or choose to create an account and/or place an order with us, we will protect your privacy and the security of your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes the terms of our commitment to your privacy.Your use of the Site is subject to the Terms of Use. What Information Asante Collect Personal identification information We may collect personal identification information from User in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when User visit the Site, register on the Site, place an order, and in connection with other activities or services, we make available on the Site. User may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. User may, however, visit the Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from User only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. User can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. Non-personal identification information We may collect non-personal identification information about User whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information. How Asante Use Collected Information To improve User serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. To personalize User experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our User as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Cookies The Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If Users do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. Security of Your InformationWe use commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative security measures and safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information. However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee, ensure, or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.
Data TransferYour information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Asante has facilities, and by subscribing to our services, you consent to the transfer of information outside of your country. Your Consent To This Privacy PolicyBy using this site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on this Site for your responsibility review. Asante may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law.
Contact InformationIf you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: support@asante.com. Last Updated: September 24, 2019
